export const ToeflData = [
  {
    question: "What is the TOEFL exam?",
    answer:
      "The TOEFL exam is the world's most widely accepted English language proficiency test, trusted by over 11,000 universities, colleges, and agencies in more than 150 countries.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the sections of the TOEFL exam?",
    answer:
      "The TOEFL exam consists of four sections: Reading, Listening, Speaking, and Writing. Each section is designed to assess your English language proficiency in different areas.",
  },
  {
    question: "How can I prepare for the TOEFL exam?",
    answer:
      "Prepare for the TOEFL exam with our comprehensive practice tests and sample questions. Familiarize yourself with the exam format, question types, and time constraints to maximize your performance on test day.",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I register for the TOEFL exam?",
    answer:
      'Register now and start your journey towards global opportunities. Click the "Register for the TOEFL Exam" button to get started.',
  },
];

export const ToeicData = [
  {
    question: "What is the TOEIC exam?",
    answer:
      "The TOEIC exam, or Test of English for International Communication, is a standardized test that measures English language proficiency in a professional context. It is used by companies and organizations worldwide to assess the English skills of employees and job candidates.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the sections of the TOEIC exam?",
    answer:
      "The TOEIC exam is divided into two main sections: Listening and Reading. The Listening section assesses your ability to understand spoken English in various professional contexts, while the Reading section evaluates your ability to comprehend written English, including business documents and correspondence.",
  },
  {
    question: "How can I prepare for the TOEIC exam?",
    answer:
      "To prepare for the TOEIC exam, use practice tests and sample questions to familiarize yourself with the test format and question types. Focus on improving your listening and reading skills through targeted exercises and review common business vocabulary and phrases.",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I register for the TOEIC exam?",
    answer:
      'Register for the TOEIC exam by visiting the official TOEIC website or contacting a local test center. Click the "Register for the TOEIC Exam" button to start the registration process and find a test date that suits you.',
  },
];

export const SatData = [
  {
    question: "What is the SAT exam?",
    answer:
      "The SAT is a standardized test used for college admissions in the United States. It assesses students' readiness for college through tests in Math, Evidence-Based Reading, and Writing, with an optional Essay section.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the sections of the SAT exam?",
    answer:
      "The SAT exam consists of three main sections: Evidence-Based Reading and Writing, Math, and an optional Essay. The Evidence-Based Reading and Writing section includes Reading and Writing & Language tests. The Math section covers both Calculator and No Calculator portions.",
  },
  {
    question: "How can I prepare for the SAT exam?",
    answer:
      "Prepare for the SAT by taking practice tests, studying key content areas, and using SAT prep books or online resources. Focus on improving your skills in Reading, Writing, and Math, and consider enrolling in a prep course if needed.",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I register for the SAT exam?",
    answer:
      'Register for the SAT exam by visiting the College Board website, where you can create an account, choose a test date, and find test centers. Click the "Register for the SAT Exam" button to begin the registration process.',
  },
];

export const IeltsData = [
  {
    question: "What is the IELTS exam?",
    answer:
      "The IELTS (International English Language Testing System) exam is a standardized test that measures English language proficiency. It is used for academic, immigration, and professional purposes and is recognized by thousands of institutions globally.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the sections of the IELTS exam?",
    answer:
      "The IELTS exam is divided into four sections: Listening, Reading, Writing, and Speaking. The Listening and Reading sections test comprehension skills, the Writing section assesses your ability to express ideas clearly in writing, and the Speaking section evaluates your spoken English.",
  },
  {
    question: "How can I prepare for the IELTS exam?",
    answer:
      "Prepare for the IELTS exam by practicing each section using official IELTS preparation materials. Take practice tests, work on your English language skills, and familiarize yourself with the test format and types of questions you will encounter. Consider taking an IELTS preparation course if you need additional help.",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I register for the IELTS exam?",
    answer:
      'Register for the IELTS exam by visiting the official IELTS website or contacting an authorized IELTS test center. Click the "Register for the IELTS Exam" button to begin the registration process, choose a test date, and find a test center near you.',
  },
];
